Time.
From forever.
this.
yes.
Gathering silence.
Are you afraid it will hurt because you wipe it so hard with your eyes?
Oh, no, no, that's not it.
I'm so thirsty that I shed a few tears
I wonder if it tastes like this, oh my
Miya, I did that without even knowing. comfort me
I think I should give it to you.
In other words, what kind of consolation are you giving?
If you ask me, you should just do that.
I think so, number 1, yes.
basic. dad.
Okay then, that's not it either.
Then, are you there today?
Huh? Hey.
Don't say anything.
Are you saying you’re going to church from now on without saying anything?
uh. under.
That one over there.
In your eyes.
Wow Bonggijeong Namdai
It's so hard, hey
Hey. uh.
Draw it. Let's see
Let's see. Oh, really?
Come to your senses.
so. I just don't know
I told you to go quickly. I'm out of my mind.
I don't even know how I got outside.
Just look at the news
Hold it and hold back your tears
Isn't it strange if you have the presence of mind to do it? bell?
Come on Jo Mirae, do you hate it?
It's okay if you don't like it.
that.
to be honest.
What about that moment?
It was comforting. wonderfully.
It's over, it's over now
official couple call holding hands
Hey, is this Lee Gak? It’s a shit day.
The special is alive and the same.
Are you saying it brought tears to my eyes?
speaking in. Who is it?
Even in the first recording, the present speaker was
It was not revealed in detail. I can't be confused
There is. What are you talking about?
Wooyeonah.
You want to meet me somewhere like this? people are weird
You see. Because it's a special day
What special day did you care about?
And what are you responsible for?
What happens if I kiss you arbitrarily?
Kiss me, don't say that.
Earlier I kissed my eyes
Just say that's it, that's it
Did you know that? what
If you really want, just now
You and I did that.
Don't come as a return.
This today?
It's confirmed.
And what do you keep taking responsibility for?
No, there is nothing you are responsible for.
It was meant to comfort me.
I think we can do that between friends.
I see it. So, no matter what you do, I will take responsibility.
my heart for you
Don't tell anyone today 2 days
If you tell me, they won't leave you alone.
Soya, I will take responsibility?
gear.
Together, I'm a fool.
uh.
Oh, really?
under.
Come sing a song.
What's wrong with you? Why are you doing this to my mom?
Is it a speaking habit?
Why does he do something he doesn't do before?
Don't answer.
When mom respects me? I'll tell you then.
What do you not know?
uh.
Why why?
No, actually, why am I so late? It’s just a coincidence.
Open it up a little bit.
You're not hanging out with bad kids again, are you?
Mom doesn't know. Why me?
Did you pretend that puberty didn't exist?
But is it too late?
My pretty and always confident mom.
Mom was my pride.
but. I
I was a child who was not good enough to be like my mother.
Because of me again. getting more and more
I became a scary mother. Still I
I couldn't hate my mom. It's late.
Let's go quickly now.
Have you seen your wife? I saw it once at a wedding.
It’s all so bad that I don’t even recognize it, right? Yongjin's
I was so excited to see you while I was in Tianjin.
The guy who talks like that is a dirty dancer.
Who would have imagined that they would get married?
My sons are being called geniuses again.
Hey, I got it from my dad. But
My daughter said she was not young. mom's ticket
I got it. I guess I can just make it a dance studio.
The hand that blocked the bet at that time.
Even if it wasn't that warm.
Would you have been able to hate your mother as much as you wanted?
Open the door quickly?
My ideal type is someone as fun and confident as you.
I guess your tastes are special, right?
if?
Hey, it's me, I went back and forth to Kapro.
Okay, what is Acaprio? Yudori,
Throw it away in the children's sweat.
With light blonde hair that sparkles in the sunlight
Deer-like eyes, deadly
red lips. sweet
Her voice has both elegance and sexiness.
Especially blondes.
Oh, I don't know, even if you don't make it, you're an idol.
Well, that's not true. Would you like to see it then?
Show me where. I'm alive. I'm alive.
Another example is this
What is this?
My ideal type is not the human world.
hmm.
What about the airport?
I like this kind of Korean community.
Um, yes
make a reservation
I'm going to do it.
Is it dyed or what?
I'll call you back.
I came, I came.
Please tell me that the university in England is not that good.
Please, what should I do? I asked for a favor from my neighborhood sister.
You are a caring man. me
I'm going to buy it, so don't stop me. Don't snore.
Oh, sister, I'm not at school right now.
Oh, you can't wear it here when you give birth.
1 pair really suits me well. That
I'm not a senior in the human theater department.
Ah, but the city number. thank you
thank you Separate extension
Yes.
Sounds fun.
A couple?
Bacaprio.
Bro, I have to return this by tomorrow.
It's cute today.
I look at it.
brother. Do I look like that?
no. It's the opposite.
Don’t you often hear people say it’s like n?
Are you going to mess with me more? Really?
Is it good? Yes
Okay.
Are you going to the military?
The phone calls the military.
Autumn leaves How can I join the army?
No, back then
Should I go? Still
So suddenly?
So how can you see me until I die
There is only one thing, right?
Next time, you have to lose, you bad guy
I confessed that I was going to go to the military anyway.
Why yes? And really
Where is your conscience in composition?
Oh, I didn't answer the phone for a day, so today
Strange man.
I don’t have one? What, what?
Is it a sound?
Won?
yes. Did you see it?
Sunset. beautiful
Control and sunset.
Why is it beautiful? suddenly
Well.
Recreate the world with the mind of an adult
I see that even the gnoll is back
I can see it, I feel like an adult
What is it? Today, my pot belly and I
Don't tell anyone.
Why are you acting like this?
What is this?Secret.
Oh, I'm an adult
The reason why
A pot belly and me and that
Because you can do it.
Wow. Goosebumps all of a sudden?
uh.
This week's concept is red. Red.
Ha, there is no red one?
red. red of passion
It must be hot because it's red so it's finally within the rules.
Color came out.
uh. ah.
Was it red?
Should I just skip it today?
Just say it.
Oh noisy, who is it?
Who would it be?
That stupid model was especially stupid.
I really only did my hair. um
It's bad.
Ah, it seems like it would splatter too much and get dirty.
Are you talking to me now? I'm over 30.
He wore such childish clothes at his age. no.
no. Even once a week is something special.
Didn’t you come here because you wanted to? Until here
Come and see what other people think.
It's disappointing, but it's disappointing.
Ah, if you can’t change, you should leave.
processing. there is.
yes.
eww.
VR is coming, it’s coming
No, no, no,
No, it's not what it is.
Quickly.
Hey, you keep
If this happens, will you resign?
yes i am embarrassed
hey i'm embarrassed
Oh yes.
Obama.
Hey, these minors will stop leaving now, right?
Now I see it's really red
It's a violation of morals. Ah, like this
Didn't I tell you to hug me?
It's been like that for a while
Understand, you are a slave to hormones.
I hope it's time. Wait a minute.
yes.
What's going on with you guys? uh
No, uh.
uh. Oh, it wasn't there anyway?
The fun of making fun of kids
I said it was cool, I did it.
Uh. I'm just starting out
It was like that. why
Are you overdoing it like that? I'm almost there
No, you saw it, you saw it more
I did it. Really don't do that. Act naturally.
didn't say
Why don't you tell anyone about that?
Tell me what it is until I die
Are you telling me not to do it and not do it? uh
Don't do it.
I'm sorry, aren't you mad?
yo. this?
Why does red suit you so well?
uh now? cute
You know what?
hello. hi?
You guys are fighting again. by chance
To the cute magic mountain today. He was worried
Does red suit you well? No.
Do I look good on it?
that's right?
It's the best.
Hey, what I was talking about earlier.
Isn't Green here yet?
Conclusion Gu Sun-woo is a coward
The kind of thing that others like to choose
You can date old Soner
None. however.
I'm going. uh.
So Green can't come today? We
Oh, I'm going to the military.
But what are you thinking?
Don't shoot what?
Please go to the bathroom.
Lurin is worried about cron
Doing it is a preference
I confessed. how
did it?my first time
Love was just like that. confess and go to the army
Did you go? Black
I'm from Octopus Passport.
Did I cross the line?
no. Sit down and I will sit down too.
Hey, I saved a scene today.
Of all the appearances of Blue I've seen so far, it was the most embarrassing.
I finally feel like a person.
I am originally a person. too
Straight. Even if people are so straight
Not good. sorry.
Green won’t accept your confession?
Looking at your smile, it looks like you have some time to spare, right?
That's not it, don't worry.
Green likes you because we are so comfortable together.
I don't know? That's right, but I confessed before I went.
Well done. It's a nice crack. Operation well
I made it. Is that so? Then
The two go really well together, that's it
You know?
Let's go in, even if there is no green, croquis
It continues.
Why are you doing this all of a sudden?
yes. This is enough to lift the mood
There's nothing, right?
pink pink body
Okay I'm blue
Fingers are straight. I
black finger popular
I have a lot of khaki
Fingers are tall.
I am brown finger
I have a lot of hair.
What should I do? Ah, why are you binge-watching?
He was more handsome. He's tall and tall
This meta and the voice are good too
Good personality, please go to the bathroom right away
They keep calling me and saying it's Greenville
Hey hey Yunho.
Next is the Great Buddha Report.
uh.
I'll show off my pebble fingers
Do you open the app when you don't have it?
The finger station is cute
Study well and take care of it
I'll ride it if you give it to me, but if you can't do it
Yes.
Seven's.
Uh huh?
It's not going well. I'm fine with it.
I am also good at guarding and jumping rope.
and. I studied hard this time
My midterm test scores also improved slightly.
It's a cut.
Marie snake figure.
Burned it. under.
He was good at bragging about himself.
I have a fear of public speaking.
But I just gave it to my sisters and brothers.
I thought I was going to show a picture.
It’s not as big a deal as you think, right? Yes.
Even when people look at me
I became brave. yes i am here
Did you bring him well? Yes.
But that day?
Why did it have to be me? Another cool guy
There were a lot of people, right?
Round. Still, I won't die.
just. when i was young
Did I look like me? I used to too.
What I want to do because I care about what others think
I always endured it. Are you my brother?
I'm young. Is it true?
Thank you for letting me join Sping.
uh.
Oh my, who is this? Sister?
It's all over now.
Sisters. Ah, it runs just fine without me.
I'll go in first.
What is fashion?
I will spread the bad meaning.
Seungho Choi. When I change it anyway
It's okay, don't worry about it, of course I
I did it. It was my mistake.
That's it, what kind of money do we have?
There is?
I have one too. and
I say yes and no.
Because I made a mistake. I
I'll buy it for you.
Are you going together?
Are you angry? Star,
So, they thought I would be angry.
Are you going oppa?
Time. Ask for more.
No, you threw two bombs at me.
I also need time to really understand my feelings.
How much time do you have? You know I have time
Not much. Hey, how do you do that?
Do you know? I'll just help you be natural. As much as me
No one knows you well, so what?
A moment to stop thinking about elephants.
It reminds me of an elephant. what?
elephant. Why our elephant?
The confession I made to you. I'll cancel for a moment.
Instead?You never
Don't feel sorry for me.
Never think about my attractiveness.
Don't ever look at me anew.
Okay?
Let's go now.
it's crazy?
I have something I want to ask.
It's a strange sound again. Oh no, no, no.
Listen.
me? in your eyes
You did that. hmm.
But I still don't know if he likes me or not. Ah,
That's a strange sound again. why is this strange
Is it a sound? How about we go over there that day?
sorry. however.
Aren’t you doing this on purpose?
It's my first time liking someone too.
That's because I don't know.
It's the first time you've ever liked someone
Do you have any enemies?
Lies, why do I lie to you?
Who believes in a kid like you?
It's never happened before, huh?
You said there wasn’t one? You’re the first.
Okay, okay, okay?
If this is what I say, I won’t believe it even if you make meju with soybeans.
But you don’t trust me that much?
Originally made from soybeans.
Then make something called watchman
making?
iced coffee.
Do I have to wear them tomorrow?
Hey, Babonggu, why do you keep hanging out with Songol?
What is it?
Because no, he's your friend
I don't even think about it. This is
I probably threw away my socks too.
It's 20 stones.
Hey, Smoothol Tool said he likes socks and he’s my friend.
I came wearing them. Take a look. Take a look.
Do something.
Hey, let me see.
Ah yes.
Don't do it. Don't do it.
Should I already adapt?
Gabon.
My grandmother came in and harassed one person in the poll.
Did you do something bad? Your dad.
Even though I ignore what I saw, it goes away.
Are you really that stupid?
Who is saying that someone couldn't do it?
Just because I didn't like English doesn't mean I'm a friend in the league.
No. When we grow apart, I'm like a friend
Hey.
I heard that, Mom.
You know, I got divorced, really.
My husband cheated on me.
Oh my, what should I do, Mina’s mom? It’s been going on these days.
I thought I couldn't come out, but I can't understand other people's psychology like this
There's a lot of interest in this?
Is this the book that our Udol buried?
I know now uh huh
We see this.
How many times? Is it a series?
Well, it's okay.
I need to buy a body. You bought it last time, it’s new
He said he came out. I usually have a pretty face when I put on makeup.
I know too. Huh, what is it? This
Confidence, but I still like it
I don't have any pimples and I like my eyes.
I came. When did you become so confident?
They say things change when you start dating.
No. Ah, today is a difficult day.
Anon or Jindo, how far did you pick it? no
No.
Is this really good?
It's the same as the last election.
It's different.
It’s the same, but why is it different?
Look.
Are you really okay?
Was I jealous, Dad? Why?
why did you do that
Is that so? Wait a minute
Stay still?
Is it pretty? Hey,
How is this?
I'll apply it.
Is it because of something?
Why are you saying that?
Do it now? That's it, now
Are you okay? What is okay?
It's okay, these are real,
It's okay now. that's right.
Are you annoying? Lol
Yes, yes, you are crying
I went through such an incredible thing, but nothing happened.
I was pathetic and annoyed that I was laughing without knowing.
Crying. Mirae is right.
If something like that had happened, you should have told me, you're my friend.
lead role.
Are you guys disappointed in me?
Do you really think we don't know each other? We really are
They are just average people.
I'm really sorry.
Am I sorry?
No, you watched and learned, no,
I'm more sorry huh?
No, me?
Do you want me to stop doing it?
Oh, you're going to die of embarrassment?
A moment to stop thinking about elephants.
It reminds me of an elephant.
What is it? Is it like a spell?
That can't be possible. no.
This is unfamiliar
No, I feel déjà vu
There is aura.
Come.
What on earth are you picking up? The report says
Oh, I always follow patterns too, huh?
I'm so scared. Are you really going to die to protect me?
Where are the real children's eyes?
Hey, hey, call Doyoung right now.
If I tell you to listen right away and go, I will tell you
Are you going to show me a picture of the comment?
What picture do you want me to take? 101 limbs
My son was so tight that I took a picture.
Yes, yes, let’s die together, call me.
Hey, call me.
Just really show it, hey
A moment to stop thinking about elephants
It reminds me of an elephant. What is this
Is it paper? Yes.
Can you please share our genealogy? Of course not
I'll give it to you later. clothes
Also, since when did he have the charm to captivate people like that?
Don't think about it. I don't know.
Why is it so familiar these days?
I'll come and go with my cell phone. Oh, I'll go with you.
If you bother to do something, I'll do it.
Be careful not to bump into them.
What don't you know?No one
In a studio without one. apollo
What if you make eye contact with Hyeonghyeong? It’s like a ghost.
Are you an elementary school student? Mom is coming home, so here you are.
Just wait.
Sincheon-dong z.
hmm.
In a studio with no one around.
When you make eye contact with the planet Apollo
Ghost. nonsense
I'm doing it.
When you make eye contact with the planet Apollo
I see ghosts. not
Let's not think about it.
Admiral Yi Sun-sin really said that.
Verb Admiral Yi Sun-sin Verb, Admiral Yi Sun-sin
General verb, General Yi Sun-sin verb.
Why is that so?
The moment when you are told not to think about the voice of someone who is as good at you as you are.
The thing that came to mind was the road, I absolutely love the country, my charm
Never go out. Absolutely new
Don't look.
All right. child. uh
Did you get wet? Hello bastard.
A moment to stop thinking about elephants.
It reminds me of an elephant.
Hey, what are you doing then?
Oh, I came to see that line, that’s it.
What if I do this, I'm going to stop you with that bastard's face?
No, I know there is no such thing
I'm proving it.
How long has it been since you came to the library?
Do people know what Gwatap really is?
Never think about my attractiveness.
But was the sauce this pretty?
Did you stretch the cotar well?
Yes, the lips are originally like this.
What? Never new me
Don't look at any picture. What are you doing? think
Stop, don't you ever feel sorry for me.
Never look at me anew.
Ah
But.
Don't think about it.
uh.
Do you hate it?
Never think about your attractiveness.
You never regret me.
Don't ever look at me anew.
I'm a bad guy too.
Oh honey. What
Can't come up this week? Oh me
What should I do because it’s hard?
Hyuk went out early in the morning to Odori now.
Wake up and get ready for school.
Oh, Jonghyun’s mom is you
I made a sandwich to give it to you to stop it.
No what country?
Even real mothers do that, you.
ruler. uh
Honey, no, no, nothing.
No, it's no big deal.
It's no big deal.
Even after that day, what about Mom?
There is no change.
Still sweet.
An existence that is not a big deal.
but. more
You won't just be hurt anymore.
I heard it was actually filmed. Ah, that seasoning is mine.
I followed you last time too. It's a big deal
I'm small, really
It's a big deal.
Oh, it's true, that squid is a hundred flowers to me.
Are you interested?
That's the best, he
It looks like you have a girlfriend.
You have the best girlfriend
How do you know that? last time
Did you see it by chance? where and how
Hey? why?
Yiruma has done well.
Oh, that's right, my penis has grown a bit, huh?
Can’t I just wait?
What about you, brother?
Ah, when is your brother coming?
Don't you know?
Well, look how hot it is. Look at it a lot.
it's okay?
I was fine. Yes.
Didn’t you call me because you were busy? no.
But what do I have to say?
I have no friends to talk to about my concerns
Because there is no one. sister
I just wanted to hear something, huh?
Okay, I don't know if I can help.
What's going on? That shopping mall
I work part-time as a model. But keep going
Should I do it or study?
Should I sell out? What should I do?
I don't know if it will work. Since the model
Would you like me to show you your photo? uh.
and. This
Yerim put it in?
Than a partnership.
I'm really jealous. not very famous
It's not even that. No, really
I'm jealous.
uh.
I'll leave it. existing
Do you know my brother? Uh.
Oh sister, reporter oppa, how did you do it?
Do you know? Let's have a croquis meeting together
There is.
Isn’t there a boy that Ji-jeong likes?
uh.
So what did you meet at a drawing meeting?
Then what about your sister?
Every time we meet, oppa
Would you like to meet?
What's wrong?Actually.
Lee Jeong-ok is my ex-boyfriend.
Uh, there was a misunderstanding between the two of us.
It's been a while, so now I only do modeling.
I'm doing it. ah.
okay. I see
Sister, if you help me just once, I won't
Is it okay? Just once at that painting meeting.
Please take me with you. Original picture of my brother
I also want to see you draw, I
I want to get along well with my brother again.
Is it rice cake, sister?
Sister, thank you for your words today.
I'll go, see you again, sister.
Okay, bye.
Is this my first time liking someone?
It's my first time. Who else do you like?
Have you never seen it?
Harsh words, you and me
Like it. just
It's okay, people like people, so eat
Does there have to be a reason?
Then I can keep liking you, right?
uh.
liar?
It's not like we're dating because of Namjeon, but you lied to me.
What do you even know?
ah.
Say something or not?
Bad huh?
My kidneys were shaking, telling me to believe it, but I never thought it would happen like this.
Got it?
Where on earth has the prince gone? uh
Uh.
okay. I left Namgi-jeong
I don't even like it. dating
Not even. also.
It doesn't suit me either.
Can I bring a friend to this week's meeting?
Yerim, are you free this week?
The person who left it behind is because you really don't know.
But does he like me? That's me
What are you talking about? What's cute and sexy
I fell in love with a woman I had. feel good
Not really. No, we wouldn't have known if we didn't know.
It appeared right in front of my eyes, so how could I just leave it there?
Why do my friends run away with full stomachs because they are good friends?
How long will a real mother never talk?
It's a thing. very that
Thanks to you, I won't be able to repay you for the rest of my life.
I owe you, thank you. Or thank you.
It will come true.
Do you like me that much, am I pretty? Again the same
Personality, I'm a crazy person who doesn't like things
Isn't it? uh?
Crazy lately. oh
What should I do?